Evangelist, please help my husband!
He has lumbar spondylitis and osteoarthritis.
He cannot walk.
He cannot lift any heavy object.
He cannot sit well.
He cannot do anything. I am the one assisting him.
He is using a lumbar corset.
Please, Evangelist, help my husband.
Even if he takes some drugs, after one hour, the pain becomes severe.
Please, help my husband. I know this is our last bus stop.
Evangelist, please help me. I cannot walk.
This pain is much. I have severe pain in my back and legs.
I have severe hotness all over my body.
If I take drugs, they will only work for one or two hours but afterwards, the pain would increase.
Please, Evangelist, help me.
It is my wife that has been helping me with everything.
I cannot walk. Please, Evangelist, help me.
What do you want God Almighty to do for you today?
I want our Lord Jesus Christ to save and heal me.
Evangelist, please. I know this is my last bus stop.
God will heal me.
Jesus Christ will save me from this problem.
Amen.
Yes, Amen.
Man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, has sent the New Morning Water to you
and as we administer it in the name of Jesus, healing, deliverance,
salvation shall be yours today, in Jesus'name.
Amen.
Father, Lord God, this is Your presence. This is Your glory, Lord.
In the name of Jesus Christ, you sickness - out!
Out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Healing Through The New Morning Water In Jesus' Name
Infirmity in this body - go out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
All over your body!
You sickness tormenting this body, disturbing this body - out, in the name of Jesus!
Come out of him, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Out of him, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Out!
Sickness, disease, osteoarthritis - out, in the name of Jesus!
In Jesus' name!
Amen.
Right now, you have been set free!
Sir, walk in the name of Jesus!
Hallelujah!
Healed Through The New Morning Water In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus! I can walk!
Thank You, Jesus!
TESTIMONY TIME
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Wow. We can already see the joy of the Lord in the face of our father!
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Our God is good!
All the time!
My name is Mr Monday Ishaka.
I am 62 years old.
I am from Delta State, Nigeria.
Thank You, Lord.
The person standing beside me is my lovely wife - Mrs Vera O. Ishaka.
The unbeatable wager of every calamity!
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Lord!
Sir, we want to hear your wonderful testimony.
Can you first of all share with us more about the problems that brought you here to The SCOAN.
Fine.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was a sickness
they call lumbar spondylosis and osteoarthritis.
I could not walk and was using a lumbar corset.
I came with an inability to walk.
I had a severe pain all over my back and to make things worse, I had a hotness in my waist
that at the worst of times, I could not withstand the heat.
I would cry to God asking Him to come and deliver me from all these problems.
I was given a series of drugs to take.
I was tired of drugs of which I told my wife, that let the will of God be done.
I knew that God would not disappoint me.
I decided to run to God of Prophet T.B. Joshua,
knowing that He was the only one who could set me free from my problem.
Thank You, Lord.
Amen. So with that faith, you came to The SCOAN last week.
Can you describe what happened to you, sir,
as the New Morning Water was ministered to you in the name of Jesus?
Last week, as you saw in the clip, I was brought in a vehicle.
The pain I experienced was very severe.
The evangelists came round to minister the Morning Water on me after asking me about my problem.
I told them everything.
They then asked me if I believed in the Morning Water to which I replied, Yes, that that was why I was here.
As the Morning Water was ministered to me, I felt a hot sensation all over my body
and saw something like a being coming out of my body.
Immediately it came out of my body, I started vomiting poisonous substances.
After that, the evangelist instructed me to rise up and walk.
I then stood up and started walking and jumping.
I started glorifying the God of T.B. Joshua!
Thank You, Jesus!
In Jesus' name I pray. Amen.
So once again, sir, tell us - ever since that encounter - it has been one week now -
what are the changes that you have seen in your life?
Oh my God!
After a week, just by looking at me, one can tell that I am fit to carry out any job I want to do.
Since then, you can see me - I can walk, jump, demonstrate.
I can bend, stoop, anything at all that you want me to do - I can do it for you.
Because I know that God has given me the glory of being in His house!
I love God so much!
Just give me a second.
Let me demonstrate for the Almighty God so that the glory of Prophet T.B. Joshua...
Oh God, you are worthy of my praise!
In Jesus' name I pray. Amen.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Wow. Indeed, actions speak louder.
We can see our father is completely restored to the glory of God.
Sir, what is your advice to our viewers concerning this New Morning Water
that God used to heal you and set you free?
Thank you.
My advice to viewers all over the world, when you are in a situation like I passed through in life,
don't cry; just believe in God.
At the accepted time, God will set you free as He has set me free today, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Amen. That's a wonderful word of advice.
Sir, the lumbar corset - you mean you have no need of it right now?
This lumbar corset, I don't need it anymore! I throw it away to the glory of God.
In Jesus' name I pray. Amen.
Amen. Thank You, Jesus Christ.
That's just hear a quick word from your wife as well.
My name is Mrs Vera Ishaka from Delta State, Nigeria.
Could you explain to us about the condition that your husband was in before?
He was having lumbar spondylosis and osteoarthritis, severe back and waist pain,
inability to lift any heavy object. He could not walk or do anything on his own.
I used to assist him as a wife and the burden was so much on me - running my business,
running the home, going everywhere - it was hell then.
When I came with him, inside the vehicle as you have seen, when I cried out to the evangelist
to help my husband, the evangelist started ministering the Morning Water on him.
That is his own experience - that he has changed.
It happened to him practically but I was there. What I saw was unbelievable.
I saw him coming out like a new born baby learning how to walk.
After some time, he started walking to the glory of God.
Since then, I don't need to bother myself anymore. I only perform my duties as a wife.
He takes care of himself.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So our mother is saying that her husband is completely healed,
walking freely to the glory of God since that encounter.
On your own part, madam, what is your advice to our viewers
concerning the New Morning Water that God used to revive and restore your husband?
The New Morning Water, as you have seen, I say, Come, taste and see that miracles are real.
It is real - very real. I am a witness.
Hallelujah!
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!